New York State Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board Decisions 5376
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board Decisions
1938-1999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board
5376
63 cubic feet
63 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Bound volumes of decisions of the New York State Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board.
5620267
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 05, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 11, 2019
Scope and Contents
This collection is boxes 1 through 63 of the NYS Unemployment Insurance Board Decisions. For boxes 64-76 see collection 5319.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5319: New York State Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board Decisions 5379: Wisconsin Unemployment Compensation Department Miscellaneous Tables
Unemployment insurance -- New York (State); New York (State). Unemployment Insurance Appeal Board.
5620267
- 103,000-111,999 (Box 1)
  - Decisions 1000-1999 Volume 11, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Volume 10 900-999, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Volume 9 800-899, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Volume 8 700-799, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Volume 7 600-699, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Volume 6 500-599, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Volume 5 400-499, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Volume 4 300-399, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Volume 3 200-299, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Volume 2 100-199, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Volume 1 1-99, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 6,400-9,399 (Box 2)
  - Decisions Volume 12 1100-1199, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Volume 13 1200-1299, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Volume 14 1300-1399, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Volume 16 1500-1599, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Volume 16 1500-1599, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Volume 17 1600-1699, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Volume 18 1700-1799, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Decisions 1800-1899, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Volume 20 1900-1999, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Volume 21 2000-2099, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Decisions 2100-2299, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 57,000-65,999 also: indexes 1945-1950 (Box 3)
  - Decisions Volume 24 2300-2399, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Volume 25 2400-2499, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Volume 26 2500-2599, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 27, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Volume 28 2700-2799, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 29 2800-2899, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Volume 30 2900-2999, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Volume 31 3000-3099, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Volume 32 3100-3199, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Volume 33 3200-3299, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- 93,000-102,999 and volumes 198-299 (36,500-37,499) (Box 4)
  - Decisions Volume 34 3300 - 3399, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Volume 35 3400-3499, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Volume 36 3500-3599, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Volume 37 3600-3699, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Volume 38 3700-3799, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Volume 39 3800-3899, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Volume 40 3900-3999, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Volume 41 4000-4099, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Volume 42 4100-4199, 1941-1944 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Volume 43 4200-4299, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Volume 44 4300-4399, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- 9,400-12,499 (Box 5)
  - Decisions Volume 45 4400-4499, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Volume 46 4500-4599, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Volume 47 4600-4699, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Volume 48 4700-4799, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Volume 49 4800-4899, 1941-1943 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Volume 50 4900-4999, 1940-1942 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Volume 51 5000-5099, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Volume 52 5100-5199, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Volume 53 5200-5299, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 54 5300-5399, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 55 5400-5499, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- 2,000-3,999 (Box 6)
  - Decisions Volume 56 5500-5599, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Volume 57 5600-5699, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Volume 58 5700-5799, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vo. 59 5800-5899, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Volume 60 5900-5999, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Volume 61 6000-6099, 1941-1945 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol. 62 6100-6199, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 63 6200-6299, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Volume 64 6300-6399, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Volume 65 6400-6499, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 66 6500-6599, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- 75,000-82,499 and codification of text 1938-1939 citations of decisions 1938-1947 (Box 7)
  - Decisions Volume 67 6600-6699, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Volume 68 6700-6799, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vol. 69 6800-6899, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 70 6900-6999, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 71 7000-7099, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 72 7100-7199, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol 73 7200-7299, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 74 7300-7399, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vo. 75 7400-7499, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 76 7500-7599, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 77 7600-7699, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- 112,000-122,491 (Box 8)
  - Decisions Vol. 78 7700-7799, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Vol. 79 7800-7899, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vo. 80 7900-7999, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 81 8000-8099, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 82 8100-8199, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 83 8200-8299, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol. 84 8300-8399, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 85 8400-8499, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vol. 86 8500-8599, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 87 8600-8699, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 88 8700-8799, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- 48,000-56,999 and indexes 1938-1944 (Box 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 89 8800-8899, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Vol. 90 8900-8999, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vol. 91 9000-9099, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 92 9100-9199, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 93 9200-9299, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 94 9300-9399, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol. 95 9400-9499, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 97 9600-9699, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vol. 98 9700-9799, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 99 9800-9899, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 82,500-92,500 and volume 295-297 - 35,000-36,499 (Box 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 111 11000-11099, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Vol. 112 11100-11199, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vol. 113 11200-11299, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 114 11300-11399, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 115 11400-11499, 1945-1946 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 116 11500-11599, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol. 117 11600-11699, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 118 11700-11799, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vol. 119 11800-11899, 1945-1946 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 120 11900-11999, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 121 12,000-12,099, 1945-1946 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- 29,000-34,499 (Box 11)
  - Decisions Vol. 100 9900-9999, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Vol. 101 10000-10099, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vol. 102 10100-10199, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 103 10200-10299, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 104 10300-10399, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 105 10400-10499, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vo. 106 10500-10599, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 107 10600-10699, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vol. 108 10700-10799, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 109 10800-10899, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 110 10900-10999, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- 25,200-28,999 (Box 12)
  - Decisions Vol. 122 12100-12199, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Vol. 123 12200-12099, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vol. 124 12300-12399, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 125 12400-12499, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 126 12500-12599, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 127 12600-12699, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol. 128 12700-12799, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 129 12800-12899, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vol. 130 12900-12999, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 131 13000-13099, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 132 13100-13199, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- 1-1,999 (Box 13)
  - Decisions Vol. 133 13200-13299, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Vol. 134 13300-13399, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vol. 135 13400-13499, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 136 13500-13599, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 138 13700-13799, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 139 13800-13899, 1946-1947 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol. 140 13900-13999, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 141 14000-14099, 1946-1947 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vol. 142 14100-14199, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vo. 143 14200-14299, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- 4,000-6,399 (Box 14)
  - Decisions Vol. 144 14300-14399, 1947-1948 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Vol. 145 14400-14499, 1947-1950 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vol. 146 14500-14599, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 147 14600-14699, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 148 14700-14799, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 149 14800-14899, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol. 150 14900-14999, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 151 15000-15099, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vol. 152 15000-15199, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 153 15200-15299, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 154 15300-15399, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- 66,000-74,499 and Indexes 1951-1954 (Box 15)
  - Decisions Vol. 155 15400-15499, 1947-1950 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Vol. 156 15500-15599, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vol. 157 15600-15699, 1947-1949 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 158 15700-15799, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 159 15800-15899, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 160 15900-15999, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol. 161 16000-16099, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 162 16100-16199, 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vol. 163 16200-16299, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 64 16300-16399, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 65 16400-16499, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- 12,500-15,999 (Box 16)
  - Decisions Vol. 166 16500-16599, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Vol. 167 16600-16699, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vol. 168 16700-16799, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 169 16800-16899, 1948-1949 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 170 16900-16999, 1947-1948 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 171 17000-17099, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol. 172 17100-17199, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 173 17200-17299, 1948-1949 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vol. 174 17300-17399, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 175 17400-17499, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 176 17500-17599, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- 122,500-132,499 (Box 17)
  - Decisions Vol. 177 17600-17699, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Vol. 178 17700-17799, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vol. 179 17800-17899, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 180 17900-17999, 1948-1951 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 181 18000-18099, 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 182 18100-18199, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol. 183 18200-18299, 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 184 18300-18399, 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vol. 185 18400-18499, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 186 18500-18599, 1949-1950 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 187 18600-18699, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- 37,500-47,999 (Box 18)
  - Decisions Vol. 188 18700-18799, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Vol. 189 18800-18899, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vol. 180 18900-18999, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 191 19000-19099, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 192 19100-19199, 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 193 19200-19299, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol. 194 19300-19399, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 195 19400-19499 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vol. 196 19500-19599, 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 197 19600-19699, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 198 19700-19799, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- 15,600-18,799 (Box 19)
  - Decisions Vol. 199 19800-19899, 1949-1951 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Vol. 200 19900-19999, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vol. 201 20000-20099, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 202 20100-20199, 1949-1950 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 203 20200-20299, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 204 20300-20399, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol. 205 20400-20499, 1949-1950 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 206 20500-20599, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vol. 207 20600-20699, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 208 20700-20799, 1949-1950 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 209 20800-20899, 1949-1950 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- 22,000-25,199 (Box 20)
  - Decisions Vol. 210 20900-20999, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Vol. 211 21000-21099, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vol. 212 21100-21099, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 213 21200-21299, 1949-1950 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 214 21300-21399, 1949-1951 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 215 21400-21499, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol. 216 21500-21599, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 217 21600-21699, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vol. 218 21700-21799, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 219 21800-21899, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 220 21900-21999, 1949-1950 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- 18,800-21,999 (Box 21)
  - Decisions Vol. 221 22000-22099, 1949-1950 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Vol. 222 22100-22199, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vol. 223 22200-22299, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 224 22300-22399, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 225 22400-22499, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 226 22500-22599, 1950-1951 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol. 227 22600-22699, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 228 22700-22799, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vol. 229 22800-22899, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 239 22900-22999, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 231 23000-23099, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- 133,000-140,999 (Box 22)
  - Decisions Vol. 232 23100-23199, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Vol 233 23200-23299, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vol. 234 23300-23399, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 235 23400-23499, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 236 23500-23599, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 237 23600-23699, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol. 238 23700-23799, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 239 23800-23899, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vol. 240 23900-23999, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 241 24000-24099, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 242 24100-24199, 1950-1951 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- 141,000-144,999 and UCV - volumes 1 and 2 CCFE - volumes 1-3 TEC - volume 1 TUC - volume 1 TXD - volume 1 (Box 23)
  - Decisions Vol. 243 24200-24299, 1950-1951 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Vol. 244 24300-24399, 1950-1951 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vol. 245 24400-24499, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 246 24500-24599, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 247 24600-24699, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vol. 248 24700-24799, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol. 249 24800-24899, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 250 24900-24999, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vol 251 25000-25099, 1950-1951 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vol. 252 25100-25199, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 253 25200-25299, 1950-1951 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- 1) UCFE 15,000-24,999 2) Miscellaneous MDT, TEC, TXD, UCV, UCX ND (Box 24)
  - Decisions Vol. 254 25300-25399, 1950-1951 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Decisions Vol. 255 25400-25499, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Decisions Vol. 256 25500-25599, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Decisions Vol. 257 25600-25699, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Decisions Vol. 258 25700-25799, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Decisions Vo. 259 25800-25899, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Decisions Vol. 260 25900-25999, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Decisions Vol. 261 26000-26099, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Decisions Vol. 262 26100-26199, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Decisions Vo. 263 26200-26299, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Decisions Vol. 264 26300-26399, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Decisions Vol. 265 26400-26499, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Decisions Vol 266 26500-26599, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Decisions Vol. 267 26600-26699, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Decisions Vol. 268 26700-26799, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Decisions Vol. 269 26800-26899, 1951-1952 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Decisions Vol. 270 26900-26999, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Decisions Vol. 271 27000-27099, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Decisions Vol. 272 27100-27199, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Decisions Vol. 273 27200-27299, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Decisions Vol. 274 27300-27399, 1951-1952 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Decisions Vol. 275 27400-27499, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Decisions Vol. 277 27600-27699, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Decisions Vol. 277 27600-27699, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Decisions Vol. 278 27700-27799, 1951-1953 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Decisions Vol. 279 27800-27899, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Decisions Vol. 279 27800-27899, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Decisions Vol. 281 28000-28499, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Decisions Vol. 282 28500-28999, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Decisions Vo. 283 29000-29499, 1952-1953 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Decisions Vol. 284 29500-29999, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Decisions Vol. 285 30000-30499, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Decisions Vol. 286 30500-30999, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Decisions Vol. 287 31000-31499, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Decisions Vol. 288 31500-31999, 1952-1953 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Decisions Vol. 289 32000-32499, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Decisions Vol. 290 32500-32999, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Decisions Vol. 291 33000-33499, 1952-1953 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Decisions Vol. 293 34000-34499, 1952-1953 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Decisions Vol. 292 33500-33999, 1952-1953 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Decisions Vol. 294 34500-34999, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Decisions Vol. 295 35000-35499, 1952-1953 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Decisions Vol. 296 35500-35999, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Decisions Vol. 297 36000-36499, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Decisions Vol. 298 36500-36999, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Decisions Vol. 299 37000-37499, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Decisions Vol. 300 37500-37999, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Decisions Vol. 301 38000-38599, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Decisions Vol. 302 38600-38999, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Decisions Vol. 303 39000-39499, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Decisions 304 39500-39999, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Decisions 305 40000-40499, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Decisions 306 40500-40999, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Decisions 306 40500-40999, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Decisions 308 41500-41999 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Decisions 309 42000-42499, 1953-1954 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Decisions 310 42500-42999, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Decisions 311 43000-43499, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Decisions 312 43500-43999, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Decisions 315 45000-45499, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Decisions 313 44000-44499, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Decisions 314 44500-44999, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Decisions 316 45500-45999, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Decisions 317 46000-46499, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Decisions 318 46500-47219, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Decisions 319 46556-47499, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Decisions 320 47500-47999, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Decision 321 48000-48499, 1954-1955 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Decisions 322 48500-48999, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Decisions 323 49000-49499, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Decisions 324 49500-49999, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Decisions 325 50000-50499, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Decisions 326 50500-50999, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Decisions 327 51000-51499, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Decisions 328 51500-51999, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Decisions 329 52000-52499, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Decisions 330 52500-52999, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Decisions 331 53000-53499, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Decisions 332 53500-53599, 1955-1956 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Decisions 333 54000-54499, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Decisions 334 54500-54599, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Decisions 335 55000-55499, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Decisions 336 55500-55999, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Decisions 337 56000-56508, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Decisions 338 56509-56999, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Decisions 339 57000-57499, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Decisions 340 57500-57999, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Decisions 341 58000-58499, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Decisions 342 58500-58999, 1956-1957 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Decisions 352 63529-63999, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Decisions 351 63000-63528, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Decisions 350 62507-62999, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Decisions 349 62000-62506, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Decisions 348 61500-61999, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Decisions 347 61000-61499, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Decisions 346 60500-60999, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Decisions 345 60000-60499, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Decisions 344 59500-59999, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Decisions 343 59000-59499, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Decisions 353 64000-64499, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Decisions 354 64500-64999, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Decisions 356 65500-65999, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Decisions 357 66000-66559, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Decisions 355 65000-65499, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Decisions 358 66560-66999, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Decisions 359 67000-67499, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Decisions 360 67500-67999, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Decisions 361 68000-68499, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Decisions 362 68500-68999, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Decisions 372 73500-73999, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Decisions 371 73000-73499, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Decisions 370 72500-72999, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Decisions 369 72000-72499, 1959-1960 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Decisions 71500-71999, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Decisions 367 71000-71499, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Decisions 366 70500-70999, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Decisions 365 70000-70499, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 8)